原创翻译  双语字幕
《少年谢尔顿》前情提要
Previously on Young Sheldon...
最新连载海外影视剧字幕下载
请登陆 www.yysub.net
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
玛丽·库珀
Mary Cooper...
"我要跟你爽一发"
I want to sex you up.
翻译     全新矿卡赛太公   油腻希
我有好消息
I have good news.
校对     男翻译自用款赛
很好  我很需要好消息
Good. I could use it.
我在保龄球馆找到了工作
I got a job at the bowling alley.
后期      灰灰是菇凉      时间轴    加森
跟布兰达一起工作吗
Working with Brenda?
每天呢
Every day.
今天的事我深感抱歉
I am so sorry about today.
总监     新浪微博@赛太公
我不愿看到你离主而去
I just hate to see you walk away from the Lord.
感觉是祂离我而去了
Feels like he's walking away from me.
这是什么
What is that?
即食汉堡面
Hamburger Helper.
看来是真的了  我们是穷人
It's official. We're poor.
我们不穷
We're not poor.
这里面有汉堡肉
There's hamburger in there.
这里面有汉堡肉的  对吧
There's hamburger in there, right?
我很喜欢即食汉堡面啊
I like Hamburger Helper.
能快速帮你把汉堡肉做成一顿美味餐点
It really does help your hamburger make a great meal.
你喜欢那就太好了
Well, it's a good thing you like it,
因为你是真的穷
'cause you're definitely poor.
-像我们一样  -我们家没问题
- Like us. - We're fine.
-其实...  -吃你的饭吧
- Actually... - Just eat.
-我们还做饭前祷告吗  -为何不做
- Do we still say grace? - Why not?
因为妈妈最近暂时跟教会断绝往来了  妈妈
Mom's been taking a break from the church. Mom?
我还没仔细想过这件事
Well, I hadn't really thought about it.
想要的话可以说啊
We can if you want to.
就别了吧
Let's not.
虽然这件事很没意义
As meaningless as it is,
但仪式感能令我感到安心
I do find the ritual comforting.
赶紧有个人做决定吧  这坨饭要冷了
Well, somebody make a decision. That slop's getting cold.
无论冷的还是热的都好吃  就像早餐麦片
No, it's good cold or hot, like Grape-Nuts.
可以让我来说吗
Ooh, can I say it?
当然
Sure.
感谢您赐给我们面前的食物
Bless us Lord for the food we are about to receive
也请保佑为我们准备食物的人
and bless the hands that prepared it.
再拜托保佑我这周拍照日  我的秀发状态完美
And let me have a good hair day for school pictures later this week.
-我想想还有什么事要求...  -赶紧收尾
- Let's see, what else do I want... - Wrap it up.
保佑我爸能在有线电视被停机前
And please let my dad find a full-time job
找到一份全职工作  阿门
before we lose cable. Amen.
阿门
Amen.
♪ 世上没人比我强壮 ♪
♪ Nobody else is stronger than I am ♪
♪ 昨天我移了一座山 ♪
♪ Yesterday I moved a mountain ♪
♪ 我相信我能当你的英雄 ♪
♪ I bet I could be your hero ♪
♪ 我是个了不起的小家伙 ♪
♪ I am a mighty little man ♪
少
年
谢尔顿
所以...
So...
所以你不上教堂的这事怎么样了
how's it going with this whole no church thing?
有一点说不清
It's a little weird,
但我会想通的
but I'm figuring it out.
你觉得你可能会回去吗
Think you might go back?
还不知道呢
I don't know yet.
还是会换一间教堂
Maybe find a different church?
我不知道  乔治
I don't know, George.
我拿瓶啤酒
I'm gonna get a beer.
你...
You, uh,
要像以前那样加入我一起吗
care to join me like the good ol' days?
我只是不上教堂
Just 'cause I'm not going to church
不代表我会立刻开喝好吗
doesn't mean I'm suddenly a drinker.
好吧  行
Okay. Well, then I guess
那我跟我的兄弟们跟你说声晚安啦
me and my friends will say goodnight.
我们需要谈谈
We need to talk.
谈什么
About what?
你帮我们家报税  我们状况多糟了
You do their taxes. How bad off are we?
根据他们打零工的收入
Based on their part-time income,
我们家大概在年底前就会把钱花光
we're going to run out of money by the end of the year.
-在圣诞前还圣诞后啊  -前
- Before or after Christmas? - Before.
我可不想听到这种消息
Not what I wanted to hear.
我们有什么能帮忙的吗
Anything we can do to help?
或许可以变卖我们的东西
Perhaps we could sell our stuff.
可是我喜欢我的东西
But I like my stuff.
我也喜欢自己的东西
I like my stuff, too.
再继续想想吧
Let's keep thinking.
你好
Hello?
康妮  我是格兰特·林克莱特
Connie. Grant Linkletter.
你好啊  格兰特
Hello, Grant.
找我有什么事啊
What can I do for you?
我看日历的时候发现离我上次约你
Well, I looked at my calendar and realized it's been six weeks
已经过去六周了  所以...
since I last asked you out, so
我决定再打来试试看
I thought I'd give it another shot.
你每六周来尝试约我一次吗
You ask me out every six weeks?
以前是每九周  但我们毕竟一天比一天老了
Used to be nine, but we're not getting any younger.
这样吧...
I'll tell you what...
行
fine.
-真的吗  -试试看呗
- Really? - Why not?
太好啦
Excellent.
但我先说清楚啊
But I want to be clear,
我们约会就只是...  怎么叫来着
this is just one of those-- whatcha call it--
柏拉图式啊
uh, platonic things.
我们就是单纯吃个饭
We're just having dinner.
我接受
I'll take it.
那你是倾向去餐厅吃
Now, would you prefer a restaurant
还是吃点家常菜呢
or some good home cooking?
我会煲七种汤呢
I make seven kinds of soup.
我觉得就出去吃吧
I think I'll just stick with a restaurant.
没问题
Fair enough,
但总有一天  你会尝到我的蘑菇大麦汤
but one day, you'll try my mushroom barley,
让你的味蕾绝顶升天
and your taste buds will swoon.
晚安吧  格兰特
Good night, Grant.
秘诀就在我长时间熬煮洋葱
The secret is how long I cook the onions.
鸡窝  现在
Chicken coop, now.
你来了
Hi.
我们这是在搞什么鬼
What are we doing?
你才搞什么鬼呢
What are you doing?
怎么  你请了玛丽到保龄球馆工作
What, you hired Mary to work at the bowling alley.
她需要工作啊
She needed a job.
我当好人也有错吗
I was being nice.
你不觉得有点怪吗
Well, you don't think it's a little weird?
我俩  在这里
This right here--
哪哪都怪好吗
it's all weird.
你喝醉了吗
Are you drunk?
是不够醉好吗
Not nearly enough.
你跟玛丽一起工作糟到不能再糟了  毕竟我们...
You and Mary working together is a bad idea considering...
你懂  我俩...
you know, you and me.
我们什么都没做  乔治
We haven't done anything, George.
但曾经差点阴错阳差...  你知道有过那瞬间
But there was considering. You know there was.
那你是要我怎么样
What do you want me to do?
要我炒了她吗
You want me to fire her?
不用  那多怪啊
No, no. That'd be weird.
那刚才讲的不全是废话吗  晚安
Which is exactly where we started. Good night.
你懂我是什么意思吧
You understand what I'm saying.
我懂
说说看  你有什么技能
Okay, so what are you good at?
我很受欢迎
I'm popular.
那不算是技能
That is not a skill.
-但你就做不到啊  -行吧
- You can't do it. - Fine.
你可以去上游戏节目《危险边缘》啊
Oh, you could go on Jeopardy!
才不要  我不喜欢它们看答案猜问题的模式
Never. I don't like answers in the form of questions.
我喜欢我的答案以答案的形式呈现  而我的问题
I like my answers in the form of answers, and my questions
就以问题的形式呈现即可  谢了
in the form of questions, thank you.
或许我可以卖剧本故事
Ooh, perhaps I could sell story ideas
给电视剧  比如《星际旅行》
to TV shows like Star Trek.
你真的觉得他们会听一个小孩的主意吗
Do you really think they'd listen to a kid?
我的声音近来低了很多
My voice has gotten deeper.
那天我接电话
The other day, I answered the phone,
对方没有再把我错认成妈妈了
and they didn't mistake me for Mom.
《星际旅行》不会买你的傻供故事情节的
Star Trek's not gonna buy your stupid ideas.
我们走着瞧
We'll see about that.
我有一个故事是进取号
I have one where the Enterprise
掉进时光隧道里
falls into a time tunnel,
沃尔夫中尉变成了
and Worf becomes a Worf
12分钟后未来的自己
from 12 minutes in the future.
也可以收一次一块钱让人揍你一拳
We could let people punch you for a buck.
不行  赚的钱最后都得花去医药费
No, all our profit would just go to medical expenses.
你好啊  布兰达  我在算这一季的帐
Hey, Brenda, I was trying to do the books for the quarter,
有一个部分的帐我不是太能理解...
and I was having a little trouble making sense of it.
玛丽啊  如果
You know, Mary, if...
这工作太一团乱
if it's too big of a mess, and
你想去别的地方工作  我绝不会怪你
you'd rather work somewhere else, I'd understand.
才没有  我能搞明白的
No, I'll figure it out.
那就好
Great.
你在这里工作我真是太开心了
So happy you're here.
你怎么来啦
Hey, there.
你好啊  玛丽
Hi, Mary.
终于找到一颗不是粉色的轻球了
Finally found an eight-pounder that's not pink.
我不知道你打保龄球啊
I didn't know you bowled.
我也不知道你打保龄球啊
I didn't know you did either.
其实我呢...  现在在这工作
Actually, I, um, I work here now.
这样啊  了解
Oh, sure, okay.
我...
I...
我很遗憾
I'm so sorry
教堂的情况发展到这一步
about how things went down at church.
如果能安慰到你  你走了之后教堂也大不如前
If it helps at all, the place has gone to heck since you left.
那太好啦
Good.
我相当怀念跟你共事的时候啊
I sure do miss working with you.
我们还是可以当朋友啊
Well, we can still be friends,
哪怕现在不一起工作了
even if we don't work together.
太好了
I'd like that.
你找到小孩球了吗
You find a kiddie ball yet?
不是因为我举不起重球  只是...
It's not about the weight, just...
我手指比较小而已
I have small fingers.
玛丽  她是香农
Oh, uh, Mary, this is Shannon.
-香农  她是玛丽·库珀  -你好
- Shannon, this is Mary Cooper. - Hi.
你以前叫玛丽·塔克对吧
You used to be Mary Tucker.
不这么叫好多年啦
Oh, not in a long time.
你还记得我吗
You remember me?
抱歉  不记得
Sorry, no.
我是香农·狄克森  你以前当过我保姆
Shannon Dixon. You used to babysit me.
是吗
Is that so?
她人最好了
She was so great.
她都会准我看电视到很晚
She would let me stay up late and watch TV
然后自己忙着跟男朋友亲热去
while she would make out with her boyfriend.
我不...  记得这些事了呢
I don't... remember any of that.
你不记得也不奇怪  你也没少去我爸酒柜里拿酒喝
Oh, I'm not surprised. You used to hit my dad's liquor cabinet pretty hard.
没想到啊  玛丽·库珀
Well, Mary Cooper.
我当年很年轻  还没认识主
I was... young and hadn't found the Lord.
祝你们两个玩得愉快啊
You two have a great time.
就是这张发票
Here's that invoice.
谢谢啦
Oh. Great.
今天罗伯牧师又来啦
I see Pastor Rob's here again.
他...
Oh, does, uh...
他常常来光顾吗
does he come here often?
常  但不是跟这妞
Not with that one.
她是新妞
She's new.
那他很厉害啊
Well, good for him.
单身  长相不错的牧师
Single, good-looking pastor.
在我们这样的小镇
In a small town like this,
魅力简直就跟罗杰·斯陶巴差不多啊
he might as well be Roger Staubach.
天啊  我们达拉斯牛仔队的超级巨星啦
Oh, my God. The Dallas Cowboys.
当然  懂了
Oh, sure, course.
如果还有什么需要就来找我
Um... hey, if you need me,
我先回去后面办公室做点...
I'm gonna be in the office doing...
办公室的事
office things.
你来干嘛
What are you doing here?
我家的啤酒喝完了
I ran out of beer at home,
我懒得专程跑去商店买
didn't feel like driving to the store.
所以你就大大方方走进我们家自己拿吗
Oh, so you just waltz in and help yourself?
大概就是这情况
'Bout sums it up.
我要换个门锁
I'm changing the locks.
干杯
Cheers.
我的女儿还好吗
So, how's my daughter doing?
她感觉还行吧
Eh, she seems okay.
还在试图摸索出一条道路
Still trying to figure things out.
我实话实说  家里少了点宗教氛围
I got to be honest, I'm not exactly upset
我可是没有任何反对意见
about less religion in the house.
我懂你
I hear you.
虽然  我靠着耶稣这张牌
Although, Jesus making her forgive me
也让她原谅过我好多次
has come in handy more than a few times.
我懂  我也打过这张牌
Yeah, I played that card, too.
话说回来  我还记得玛丽信教前的样子
Then again, I remember Mary before God got His mitts on her, and
她可真是够野的
...she was pretty wild.
这不用你说
Don't have to tell me.
我当年就是她野的对象
I was the person she was wild with.
她在认识你很久之前就野了好吗
Oh, she was wild long before she ever met you.
你什么意思
What do you mean?
你觉得你是她第一个野的对象吗
Did you think that you were the first person she was wild with?
这个...  难道不是吗
Well... yeah.
当进取号马上要被
And just when the Enterprise is about to be
博格人给同化时
assimilated by the Borg,
另一艘星舰现身了  由卫斯理·克拉希尔所掌舵
another ship appears, piloted by Wesley Crusher.
-嗯哼  -这很令人惊讶
- Uh-huh. - It's surprising because
因为卫斯理·克拉希尔离开节目很久了
Wesley Crusher left the show years ago,
他的回归是大事
so it's a big deal.
你说大就大
If you say so.
还有呢  数据少校...
I have more. Commander Data...
我要预定晚餐位子
I'd like a reservation for dinner.
好的  我可以等
Yes, I'll hold.
你想晚餐的时候详聊吗  行
You want to do this over dinner? Okay.
我今晚要带你姥姥出去约会
I'm taking your grandmother out tonight.
她没跟我说过啊
She didn't mention it to me.
或许因为这事情跟你无关
Maybe because it doesn't concern you.
我的姥姥  我的教授
My meemaw, my professor--
你们两个人的交点是谁呢
who's in the middle of that Venn diagram?
是的  晚上八点  两个人
Yes, two people at 8:00.
八点对姥姥来说太晚了
8:00's a little late for Meemaw.
她喜欢几点吃饭呢
What time does she like to eat?
她跟你一个年纪  所以最晚六点半
Well, she's old like you, so 6:30 at the latest.
我们可以改订六点半吗  谢谢
Can we make that 6:30? Wonderful.
等等  她喜欢吃法国菜吗
Hold on. Does she like French food?
我之后再打给你
I'll call you back.
言归正传  数据少校...
Anyway, Commander Data...
我问你个问题  如果这个数据少校
Let me ask you a question, if this Commander Data
想约你姥姥出去吃饭  他们会去哪吃呢
were taking your meemaw out for dinner, where would they go?
应该会是在全息甲板上吧
Almost certainly the holodeck.
听起来好潮啊
Sounds trendy.
那地方是在休斯顿吗
Is that in Houston?
你好
Hello.
你有什么事
What's up?
我看见外面挂着"找帮手"的牌子
I saw your "Help wanted" sign.
我想帮忙
I'd like to help, please.
你贵庚
How old are you?
几岁才能在这里打工
How old do I need to be?
14岁
14.
难道我看起来未满14吗
Do I not look 14?
-其实我不在乎  -好极了
- I don't care. - Perfect.
那我几时开始上班
So, when do I start?
等等  你真的喜欢漫画吗
All right, hold on, do you even like comic books?
当然啊
Yeah.
你最喜欢哪部漫画
What's your favorite?
X战警最酷的地方不仅是拥有超能力
And the cool thing about the X-Men is not just that they have superpowers,
他们还代表着想要在社会...
but they act as a metaphor for outsiders...
在社会找到立足之地的边缘群体
...outsiders trying to find their place in society.
你最喜欢哪个战警
Who's your favorite?
全部
All of them.
我也是
Mine, too.
我得到那份工作了
And I got the job.
你不能在漫画书店打工
You can't work at the comic book store.
最应该在漫画书店打工的人
If anyone should work at the comic book store,
是我啊
it should be me.
抱歉  我们不需要请人了
Sorry, we're not hiring.
至少能给我打点折吧
Do I at least get a discount?
我就有折扣
I do.
你好啊
Oh, hey, hi.
你还好吧
Oh... You okay?
不太好
Not really.
这几天挺难熬的
It's been a... rough couple of days.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
谢谢关心
Thank you.
如果这么说能安慰你一下
Makes you feel better,
虽然我这几天过得尚算舒心
I've had a pretty good couple of days,
但我仍打算买醉
and I'm still gonna get drunk.
你想一起去吗
Want to join me?
想
Yes.
那就太好了
That would be nice.
没啥好的  是凄凉
More sad than nice,
-不过我们走吧  -好
- but let's go. - Okay.
没料到你会选这家餐厅
So... this is unexpected.
我知道你喜欢玛格丽特酒
Well, I know you like margaritas,
所以我的第一反应就是墨西哥餐厅
so my first thought was a Mexican restaurant.
机智
Good thought.
但我猜其他男人得出过同样的结论
But I assumed other men had come to that same conclusion.
-确实  -于是我又想到波利尼西亚菜
- They have. - Which led me to Polynesian fare.
我喜欢把迈泰酒
I like to think of the Mai Tai
看成是南太平洋版的玛格丽特酒
as the margarita of the South Pacific.
你从不因心血来潮而行事  对吗
You don't do anything on a whim, do you?
我试过一次  但我不喜欢结果
Did once, didn't like it.
我构思了一集《星际旅行》的剧情
I have an idea for a Star Trek episode
我想说给你听
I'd like to present to you.
为什么是我
Why me?
因为我希望能卖出去
Because I'm hoping to sell it,
由于这会在电视上播出
and since it's going to be broadcast television,
我想确保头脑简单的普通观众也能看懂
I want to make sure the common man can understand it.
我懂我刚被狠狠地羞辱了
Well, I understand I was just insulted.
太棒了  我算找对头脑简单之人了
Excellent, I came to the right common man.
故事从参宿七附近的一颗气体巨星开始
We start on a gas giant in the vicinity of Rigel IV,
接着画面中出现一艘太空梭
then see a shuttlecraft,
在一片漆黑的太空只见这个银色小圆点
a dot of silver against the inky blackness of space.
在太空梭内
Inside the shuttlecraft,
我们看到沃尔夫中尉呼吸困难
we see Lieutenant Worf struggling to breathe.
他感染上一种险恶的智能真菌
He's been infected by a vicious intelligent fungus.
-你要去哪  -我在听啊
- Where are you going? - I'm listening.
咳咳  咳咳
Cough, cough.
沃尔夫被孢子呛得喘不过气
Worf is choking on spores,
但这可不是寻常孢子
but not just your everyday spores,
-这种孢子自有其邪恶目的  -是哦
- these are spores with their own evil agenda. - Uh-huh.
当他陷入昏迷时  一个身穿宇航服的
And, as he sinks into a coma, a mysterious figure
神秘人物走到他跟前
in a spacesuit approaches.
他降下头盔面窗  露出...
He lowers the visor of his helmet revealing...
未来沃尔夫的脸  你被剧情迷住了吗
Future Worf. Are you hooked?
沉迷不已呢
Oh, yeah.
片头字幕出现
Main titles.
接着响起主题曲  扮演皮卡德舰长的男星
Cue theme song and the soothing voice
帕特里克·斯图尔特用抚慰的声音说
of Patrick Stewart as Captain Picard says...
"宇宙
"Space..."
人类最后的边疆"
...the final frontier."
帕特里克·斯图尔特是哪位
Who's Patrick Stewart?
-心情好点了吗  -我没事啦
- Feeling better? - I'm fine,
之前只是有些小郁闷
just having a little moment earlier.
是吗
Oh, yeah.
好吧
All right.
看来偶遇到罗伯牧师
Seems like running into Pastor Rob kind of...
让你有点心神不定
kind of rattled you a little bit.
这个嘛
Oh, well...
我被要求离开教会
I was asked to leave the church,
他却还待在那里
and he's still there, so...
我的心伤还没愈合
it's still a little fresh.
我懂
Yeah, I get that.
-不过他看起来人挺好的  -是的
- Seems like a nice guy, though. - Oh, yeah,
他人很好
he's great.
长得又帅
Cute as a button.
算是吧
I guess.
我个人更喜欢块头大点的男人
I prefer a bigger man.
象乔治这种吗
Like George?
没错  越壮硕越好
Oh, yeah. Bigger the better.
在进取号控制室深处
Deep within the Enterprise's control room,
未来沃尔夫说道
Future Worf says,
"为了这次任务
"I willingly sacrifice myself
我甘愿牺牲自己"
for the good of this mission,"
说完便纵身跃进曲速核心
then throws himself into the warp core.
超光速粒子发生爆炸
There's an explosion of tachyons.
进取号将一大片真菌炸个精光
The Enterprise blasts free of the gigantic field of fungus.
画面淡出
Fade out.
编剧  谢尔顿·李·库珀
Written by Sheldon Lee Cooper.
你觉得怎么样
What do you think?
如果这位沃尔夫老哥在太空梭里被感染了
If this Worf fella was infected on the shuttles,
他为什么要回到进取号
why would he come back to the Enterprise
将其他人都置于危险之中
and put everyone else in danger?
啊这...
Well...
我父亲发现了我故事里的漏洞
My father found a flaw in my story,
我妹妹有一份我羡慕不已的工作
my sister had a job I envied.
今天对头脑简单的普通人来说意义非凡
It was a big day for the common man.
但随即我突然萌生出一个想法
But then I had an idea that,
和未来沃尔夫一样  超前于时代
like Future Worf, was ahead of its time.
-米希  -干嘛
- Missy. - What?
一张一元钞为什么价值一美元
Why is a dollar worth a dollar?
谢尔顿  我很忙好吗
Sheldon, I'm busy.
我也很忙  我解决了我们所有的金钱问题
Me too. I've solved all of our money problems.
我要发明我自己的一套数字货币
I'm going to invent my own digital currency.
你是指自己印钱吗
Like, printing your own?
不是  首先我们给难以发现的数字赋值
No. First, we assign value to difficult-to-find numbers
将它们存放于计算机数据库中
and store them in a computer database.
然后创建算法来开采这些数字
Then we create an algorithm to mine the numbers,
接着鼓励人们由政府支持的货币
then we encourage people to switch from currencies
转而使用我们的货币
that are government-backed to ours.
太天才了  我要发达了
It's brilliant. I'm going to be rich.
说起发达
Speaking of,
你知道蝙蝠侠私底下也是个高富帅吗
did you know Batman is also secretly a rich dude?
或者他只是住在一个有钱佬的地下室里
Or he lives in a rich dude's basement.
我还没弄明白
I'm still figuring it out.
谢谢你  提基小姐
Oh, thank you, tiki woman.
波利尼西亚神话中人类的始祖
话说
So...
你在忙什么工作
what's going on at work?
我不想聊枯燥的科学话题  怕你无聊
I don't want to bore you with science talk.
不啊  我很有兴趣
No, no, I'm interested.
太好了  我们正在和芬兰团队竞争
Excellent. We're in a race with the Finnish team to see
看谁能纠正轻粒子的统一性
who can correct the unification of the leptons.
你能想象到  全世界都在焦急地等待
As you can imagine, the world waits anxiously
看谁先冲过终点线
while we see who crosses the finish line first.
这么说芬兰[终点]团队可能在终点线咯
So, the Finnish may be at the finish line?
你不仅人美  还那么诙谐
Oh, you're witty, too.
你钓男人的手段真多样
More cheese to bait the trap.
我们该点菜了吧
Maybe we should order dinner.
说什么傻话呢  这里不就有食物了吗
Nonsense, there's food right here.
菠萝
Pineapple,
外层多刺
prickly on the outside,
但内里却如此美丽
but beautiful inside,
和你一样
just like you.
你知道那个叫香农的女孩吗
And you know that Shannon girl...
和罗伯牧师一起的那个吗
With Pastor Rob?
她以前总尿床
She was a bedwetter.
都10岁了还尿床
Ten years old.
这可不正常
That's not normal.
也许他们度蜜月时  他会有"惊"喜
Maybe he'll get a fun little surprise on their honeymoon.
他们才不会结婚啦
Oh, no, they're not getting married.
你怎么知道不会
Well, how do you know?
我不知道
I don't.
我只是觉得那女孩配不上他
I just think he could do better.
玛丽·库珀
Mary Cooper.
你是不是喜欢他
Are you sweet on him?
怎么可能  说什么呢
No! What?
我可是有夫之妇
I am a married woman.
婚姻十分美满幸福
Happily.
我也结过婚  但那阻止不了我花心
Well, I was married once, too, didn't stop me from looking.
我可没花心
Well, I'm not looking.
你去哪
Where you going?
去跳舞
To dance.
我还以为浸礼教徒不跳舞呢
I didn't think you Baptists did that.
照理说我们也不该喝酒
We don't drink, neither.
你看我
Look at me. Ooh! Wow.
我能歌善舞
I'm pretty good.
你听过这句俗语吗
Are you familiar with the phrase,
-"钱滚钱需要钱吗"  -没听过
- "You need money to make money"? - No.
反正有这说法  我很聪明地把它改为
Well, it's a phrase, and my clever twist on it is,
"我要造钱来挣钱"
"I'm going to make money to make money."
我说到"造钱"时  你可能以为
Now, when I say "make money," you might think that
我是指造假币  但并非如此
I'm talking about counterfeiting, but no,
我说的是创造一种独特的去中心化
I'm talking about creating a unique decentralized
数字货币  人们可以购买持有
digital currency that people can pay to own.
听起来像诈骗
Sounds like a scam.
不  这是一种开源货币
No, it's an open-source currency
因为数学稀缺性而具有价值
that has value due to mathematical scarcity.
听起来就是在骗人
Sounds pretty scammy.
你不懂
You don't understand.
我懂
I do.
你说一些听起来很高级的废话
You say a bunch of fancy jibber-jabber,
人们不想承认
people don't want to admit
自己太笨听不懂
they're too stupid to understand,
于是就直接把钱交给你
then they give you their money.
也算对吧
Well... um... sort of.
我喜欢这想法  我们怎么开始
Love it. How do we get started?
我们只需要一台大型计算机
Well, all we need is a mainframe computer.
-一台多少钱  -全新的大概五十万美元
- How much is that? - New, about half a million dollars,
但我希望能找到二手的
but I'm hoping to find something slightly used.
时间会证明我是对的
Time will prove me right.
说出来你肯定不相信
You're not gonna believe this,
其实我的约会经验不多
but I don't go on a lot of dates.
不会吧
No.
是真的
It's true.
我年轻时战绩还过得去
Sure, I did okay as a younger man, but
但那是因为打仗了
there was a war on and
大部分健全男人都去当兵了
most of the able-bodied men were elsewhere.
知道了  你年轻时放纵过
So, you sowed some oats, I get it.
我简直毫无节制
A whole field of them.
像童话人物约翰尼·苹果籽一样到处散播我的"种子"
I was the Johnny Appleseed of oats.
行了
Okay.
但问题是
But here's the thing.
当你一直不结婚  拖到某个年纪时
Once you put off matrimony past a certain point,
女人就会开始觉得你...  怎么说来着
women start to think of you as... What's the word?
-变态吗  -就是这个词
- Creepy? - There it is.
然后你出现了
And then along comes you,
我的德州小爆竹
my little Texas firecracker,
她按自己的一套规则玩人生游戏
playing the game of life by her own set of rules.
我是爆竹  也是菠萝
I'm a firecracker, I'm a pineapple...
挺好的啊
Good for me.
我能问你个私人问题吗
Can I ask you a personal question?
希望你不要问
Oh, I wish you wouldn't.
你想跟与爱因斯坦
How would you like to make love to a man
握过手的男人做爱吗
who shook the hand of Albert Einstein?
你还是问了
And... you did.
就是这只手
This one right here.
我整整一礼拜没舍得洗
I didn't wash it for a week.
这不利于把你推销出去
Not a selling point.
失陪一下
Excuse me for a moment.
我喝多了  要去吐
I have to toss my cookies.
回来啦
Hey.
你去哪了
Where you been?
我和布兰达去跳舞了
Brenda and I went dancing.
你去跳舞
You went dancing?
没错  而且我可会扭了
Yeah, and I'm darn good at it.
行啊
Okay.
-孩子们睡了吗  -睡了
- The kids asleep? - Yep.
你想亲热一下吗
You want to fool around?
你是不是在玩我
Are you messing with me?
我是希望玩弄你
I'm hoping to.
我今天中头彩了
Well, hot diggity dog.
欢迎光临金刚漫画  我是米希
Welcome to King Kong Comics. I'm Missy.
你有什么问题可以随时找我
If you have any questions, please let me know.
我没有问题
I don't have any questions.
我比你更了解漫画
I know more about comic books than you do.
好吧  但你可能不知道
Okay. What you may not know is the new
最新一期《绿灯侠》到了
Green Lantern just came in.
还有  如果你喜欢绿色的东西  我推荐《绿箭侠》
Also, if you like green things, I recommend Green Arrow,
当然了  还有《绿巨人浩克》  他皮肤是绿色的
and, of course, the Hulk. His skin is green.
我知道  人人都知道
I know that. Everyone knows that.
你要砸东西了吗
Uh-oh, are you gonna smash things?
浩克被惹毛就会乱砸东西
That's something the Hulk does when he gets upset.
我没被惹毛
I'm not upset.
好吧  如果你有什么需要
Cool. If you need something,
就到柜台找我  那是我工作的地方
I'll be at the front counter. Where I work.